Guide to the R. Philip Hanes Papers, 1928-2010 RL.00503
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Subject Files Series, 1945?1973 and undated
  - National Foundation on the Arts and Humanities: Grants-in-Aid--Massachusetts--New Jersey, undated (Box 75)
  - National Foundation on the Arts and Humanities: Grants-In-Aid--New Mexico--North Carolina, nd.d (Box 75)
  - National Foundation on the Arts and Humanities: Grants-In-Aid--North Dakota--Puerto Rico, undated (Box 76)
  - National Foundation on the Arts and Humanities: Grants-In-Aid--Rhode Island--Virgin Islands, undated (Box 76)
  - National Foundation on the Arts and Humanities: Grants-In-Aid--Virginia--Wyoming, undated (Box 76)
  - National Foundation for the Arts and Humanities: News REleases, 1967 (Box 76)
  - National Foundation on the Arts and Humanities: Notebook, 1966 April; 1967-1868, 2 folders (Box 76)
  - National Foundation on the Arts and Humanities: Regional Opera Survey Notebook, 1967 [Appendix A], [Appendices B-C], [Appendices D-6], 3 folders (Box 77)
  - National Foundation on the Arts and Humanities Subcommittee Hearings, 1962-1965 (Box 77)
  - National Folk Festival, 1967-1968 (Box 77)
  - National Industrial Conference Board, 1962-1967 (Box 77)
  - National Music Council, 1965-1970 (Box 77)
  - National Organizations: Miscellaneous, 1957-1962 (Box 77)
  - National Recreation Association, 1959-1964 (Box 78)
  - National Repertory Theatre, 1961-1967 and undated, 2 folders (Box 78)
  - National Trust for Historic Preservation, 1965 (Box 78)
  - National Wildlife Federation, 1967-1968 (Box 78)
  - Negro, 1945-1966 (Box 78)
  - New York Times, 1958 and undated (Box 78)
  - New Republic, 1965 (Box 78)
  - New Comen Society, 1965 (Box 78)
  - North Carolina School of the Arts, 1964-1965 (Box 78)
  - North Carolina Recreation Commission, 1943-1965 (Box 78)
  - Old Dominion Foundation, 1961-1963 (Box 78)
  - Paschen and Tallchief, 1967 (Box 78)
  - Philanthropy--General, 1962-1968 (Box 78)
  - Publicity, 1961-1966 and undated (Box 79)
  - Publicity and Advertising, 1955-1963 (Box 79)
  - Questionnaires, undated (Box 79)
  - Religion and Art, 1964 (Box 79)
  - Recreation, 1963-1965 (Box 79)
  - Research Center (National Arts Information and Research Center), 1965 (Box 79)
  - Robinson, Joe, 1965-1966 (Box 79)
  - Rockefeller Brothers Fund, 1958-1965 (Box 79)
  - Ruder and Finn, 1966 (Box 79)
  - Saturday Evening Post, 1958-1961 (Box 79)
  - Sears-Roebuck, 1965 (Box 79)
  - Selling, 1963-1965 (Box 79)
  - Show, 1963 (Box 79)
  - Society of Black Composers, 1968 (Box 79)
  - Society of the Classical Guitar, 1966 (Box 79)
  - Soldner, Paul, undated (Box 79)
  - Stevens, Roger L., 1964-1965 (Box 79)
  - Taubman, Howard, 1966 (Box 79)
  - Television and Radio, 1960-1966 (Box 79)
  - Theater, 1955-1966 and undated, 2 folders (Box 80)
  - Time and Life, 1958-1961 (Box 80)
  - Twentieth Century Fund, 1966 (Box 80)
  - Unions, 1961-1963 (Box 80)
  - United States Institute for Theatre Technology, 1962-1964 (Box 80)
  - United Millionaires Association, 1964-1965 (Box 80)
  - U.S. Committee to Further American Contemporary Music, 1968 (Box 80)
  - Urban Coalition, 1968 (Box 80)
  - VanDerbeek, Stan, 1969 (Box 80)
  - Washington International Art Letter, 1963-1964 and undated (Box 80)
  - World Crafts Council, 1968 (Box 80)
  - Young Presidents Organization, 1966-1970 (Box 80)
  - Young Presidents Organization: Enterprise, 1968 (Box 80)
  - Young Presidents Organization: University for Presidents--Attendance Analysis, 1967-1968 (Box 80)
  - Young Presidents Organization: University for Presidents Faculty, 1961-1968 (Box 81)
  - Young Presidents Organization: University for Presidents--General Information, 1966-1967 (Box 81)
  - Young Presidents Organization: University for Presidents--Institute, 1967 (Box 81)
  - Young Presidents Organization: University for Presidents--Registrants, 1967-1968 (Box 81)
  - Miscellaneous, 1956-1963, June, 2 folders (Box 81)
  - Miscellaneous, 1963 July-1965, Dec and undated, 5 folders (Box 82)
- Ampersand Series: Casebooks, 1962?1987, 1977?1985
  The Ampersand Series contains records of Ampersand, Inc., a company which existed from 1976 to 1986. The series is divided into the following four sections: Casebooks, Chronological Files, Central Files, and Company Records. There appears to be much duplication of letters, many of which are photocopies, between the Chronological Files and Central Files, and to a lesser extent the Casebooks. However, the arrangement, and therefore the access points, of these letters within each section is different. To indicate the dates Ampersand was involved with a client, the inclusive dates follow the client's name. However, earlier dates may appear on folder titles as a result of background research performed by Ampersand to gather information for a client. Dates do not appear after some of the folder titles because these folders are arranged in a topical outline rather than a chronological system, which reflects the original arrangement of the casebook volumes.
  Looseleaf notebooks, which were dismantled to reduce their bulk, and some loose material pertinent to clients. Includes contracts and agreements, grants, plans, reports, recommendations, workplans, progress reports, marketing strategy, prospect lists, financial information, printed material such as pamphlets and leaflets, financial records including computer printouts, handwritten notes, clippings, press releases, questionnaires, interviews, and correspondence. Many photocopies. Arranged alphabetically by client name. Each client's files are arranged by the various categories within the original casebooks, rather than by a strict alphabetical or chronological arrangement. The material for each organization follows the basic outline: contract, workplan, questionnaire, progress report, organizational structure, and organizational development. Some of the smaller client files do not have this outline and are organized chronologically.
  - Alabama School of Fine Arts, 1982-1985: (Box 83)
    - History (Box 83)
    - Contract, Workplan, Questionnaire, Progress Report (Box 83)
    - Organizational Structure, 4 folders (Box 83)
    - Correspondence, 1982 (Box 83)
  - Alabama School of Fine Arts, 1982-1985: (Box 84)
    - Correspondence, 1983-1985 (Box 84)
    - Executive Search: Work Plan, Candidates, Correspondence (Box 84)
  - Alabama Shakespeare Festival, 1977-1981
    - Contract, Work Plan, Questionnaire, Progress Report, Organizational Structure (Box 84)
    - Organizational Development, 2 folders (Box 84)
    - Marketing Correspondence (Box 84)
  - Arts and Crafts Association, 1977-1983 (Box 85)
    - Confidential Information, 1977-1980, March (Box 85)
    - Long-range Plan, 1979-1983 (Box 85)
    - Marketing Plan Report, 1980 (Box 85)
    - Financials (Box 85)
    - Administration/Programs (Box 85)
    - Physical Plant (Box 85)
    - Public Relations (Box 85)
    - Legal Structure (Box 85)
  - Arts and Crafts Association, 1977-1983 (Box 86)
    - Board, 2 folders (Box 86)
    - Volunteers (Box 86)
    - Correspondence, 1980-1982, 2 folders (Box 86)
    - Budget (Box 86)
  - Arts Council, 1977-1985 (Box 87)
    - History, Priorities/Work Plan (Box 87)
    - Questionnaire, Survey/Interim Report (Box 87)
    - Focusing Process, 2 folders (Box 87)
    - Correspondence, 1976-1978 (Box 87)
    - Ruder and Finn (Box 87)
    - Activity Report: Bank Statements (Box 87)
    - Proposal: General Information, 1976-1977 (Box 87)
  - Arts Council, 1977-1985 (Box 88)
    - Proposal, March- Dec. 1977, 2 folders (Box 88)
    - Resources/Funding, Resources/Dev. Act., Solicitation Public Relations, 3 folders (Box 88)
    - Printed Materials, Direct Mail (Box 88)
    - Prior/Work Plan, Questionnaire, Surveys/Interviews (Box 88)
  - Arts Council, 1977-1985 (Box 89)
    - Surveys/Interviews, 2 folders (Box 89)
    - Focusing Process (Box 89)
    - Programs/Funding Requests, 5 folders (Box 89)
  - Arts Council, 1977-1985 (Box 90)
    - Programs/Funding Requests (con't) (Box 90)
    - Budgets, Research/Funding, 3 folders (Box 90)
    - Research/Developmeng Activities (Box 90)
    - Solicitation, 2 folders (Box 90)
    - Arts Council Letter and Attachments (Box 90)
  - Arts Council, 1977-1985 (Box 91)
    - Public Relations, 2 folders (Box 91)
    - Printed Material (Box 91)
    - Correspondence re Gingrich (Box 91)
    - Contract, Work Plan, Progress Report, 1978 (Box 91)
    - Organizational Structure, Organizational Development: Research (Box 91)
  - Arts Council, 1977-1985 (Box 92)
    - Organizational Development: Grantsmanship, 1979, 3 folders (Box 92)
  - Arts Council, 1977-1985 (Box 93)
    - Organizational Development: Grantsmanship, 1979, 4 folders (Box 93)
  - Arts Council, 1977-1985 (Box 94)
    - Organizational Development: Preparation Materials, 1979 (Box 94)
    - Organizational Development: Proposal Progress, 1979, 2 folders (Box 94)
    - Marketing, 1979, 2 folders (Box 94)
    - Correspondence: Ampersand/Arts Council, General, 1978-1980 (Box 94)
  - Arts Council, 1977-1985 (Box 95)
    - Vocational Arts and Crafts Center Proposal, 1979, 2 folders (Box 95)
    - Research, 1981, 2 folders (Box 95)
    - Miscellaneous, 1981 (Box 95)
    - Structure, Long-range Plans, Fund Raising, 1984 (Box 95)
  - Arts Council, 1977-1985 (Box 96)
    - Budget, Correspondence, Public Relations--Newsclippings, 1984 (Box 96)
    - Financials, 1984 (Box 96)
    - Committees of the Arts Council, 1984 (Box 96)
    - Convention and Visitors Bureau Budget, 1984 (Box 96)
    - Miscellaneous, 1984 (Box 96)
    - Contract, Grantsmanship, Structure, Tourism Development, 1985 (Box 96)
  - Arts Council, 1977-1985 (Box 97)
    - Seasons Committee, Press Coverage, 1985 (Box 97)
    - Correspondence, 1984 (Box 97)
    - Procedures, Candidates, Correspondence, 1985 (Box 97)
    - Miscellaneous: Brochures (Box 97)
    - Miscellaneous: Tourism (Box 97)
    - Clippings (Box 97)
  - Chicago City Ballet, 1983 (Box 98)
    - Contract, Work Plan, Candidates (Box 98)
    - Structure: Organizational (Box 98)
    - Correspondence (Box 98)
    - General (Box 98)
  - Dance St. Louis, 1983-1984
    - Contracts, Structure, Financials (Box 98)
    - Publicity, Candidates (Box 98)
    - Correspondence (Box 98)
  - Dance St. Louis, 1983-1984 (Box 99)
    - Legal, Sourcing Panel, Candidates (Box 99)
    - Progress Reports,Interviews, Marketing Package (Box 99)
    - Potential Candidate Summaries (Box 99)
  - Dance St. Louis, 1983-1984 (Box 100)
    - Potential Candidate Summaries, 2 folders (Box 100)
    - Search Committee (Box 100)
    - General Correspondence (Box 100)
  - Frank Holder Dance Company, 1980-1981 (Box 101)
    - Contract, Work Plan, Questionnaire, Organizational Structure, Organizational Development: Research (Box 101)
    - Organizational Development: Research (con't), 2 folders (Box 101)
    - Marketing, Correspondence (Box 101)
  - Governor's Business Council on the Arts and Humanities, 1980-1981 (Box 101)
  - Focus, 1980, Sept.-1981 May, 2 folders (Box 101)
  - Governor's Business Council on the Arts and Humanities, 1980-1981 (Box 102)
    - Purpose, Structure, Strategies-Programs, Research (Box 102)
    - Research (Con't) (Box 102)
  - Green Hill Art Gallery, 1977
    - Casebook (Box 102)
  - Hickory Museum of Art, 1980
    - Contract, Work Plan, Questionnaires (Box 102)
    - Organizational Structure, Organizational Development, Correspondence (Box 102)
  - Hunt Campaign, 1984 (Box 103)
    - General Correspondence, 1979-1984 and undated, 3 folders (Box 103)
  - Hunt Campaign, 1984 (Box 104)
    - Confidential, J. Bennett "A Celebration of the Arts," 1984, 3 folders (Box 104)
  - Hunt Campaign, 1984 (Box 105)
    - "A Celebration of the Arts" 1984, 3 folders (Box 105)
  - Hunt Campaign, 1984 (Box 106)
    - Friends of the Arts for Hunt/ New York Reception, 3 folders (Box 106)
    - Mailing List, 2 folders (Box 106)
    - Miscellaneous, 2 folders (Box 106)
  - International Wilderness Leadership Foundation, 1977-1985 (Box 107)
    - Congress, Issues, 1977-1987 (Box 107)
    - Proposals, Meetings, Donors, 1984-85 (Box 107)
  - International Wilderness Leadership Foundation, 1977-1985 (Box 108)
    - Financials/Interview Process, 1985 (Box 108)
  - Jargon Society, 1977-1980
    - Articles, Board Meetings, 1968-1977 (Box 108)
    - Board Meetings (con't), 1978-1980 (Box 108)
  - Jargon Society, 1977-1980 (Box 109)
    - Financials, 1968-1978 (Box 109)
    - Correspondence, Program/Funding Requirements, Direct Mail (Box 109)
    - Program/Funding Requirements, (con't), 2 folders (Box 109)
    - Resourses-Funding, 1970-1979, 2 folders (Box 109)
    - Public Relations, Printed Materials/Publications, Other, 1972-1978 (Box 109)
  - Metropolitan Opera 1982-1983 (Box 110)
    - 1982-1983 (Box 110)
  - Moravian Music Foundation, 1977-1978
    - Priorities, Questionnaire, Survey and Interim Report, 1975-1978 (Box 110)
    - Focusing Process, 1975-1978 (Box 110)
    - Prograams/Funding Requirements, Budgets, 1973-1978 (Box 110)
    - Resourses/Funding, 1976-1977 (Box 110)
    - Resources/Development Activities, Solicitation, 1976-1977 (Box 110)
  - Moravian Music Foundation, 1977-1978 (Box 111)
    - Solicitation (con't), 1976-1978 (Box 111)
    - Public Relations, 1976-1977, 2 folders (Box 111)
  - Museum of Ceramic Art, 1978
    - Correspondence, 1978, 2 folders (Box 111)
  - Museum of Early Southern Decorative Arts (MESDA), 1977-1978
    - Work Plan, Questionnaire,Progress Report, 1977-78 (Box 111)
    - Organizational Development: Research, 1977-1978 (Box 111)
  - Museum of Early Southern Decorative Arts (MESDA), 1977-1978 (Box 112)
    - Organizational Development: Grantsmanship, Marketing, General Correspondence (Box 112)
  - North Carolina Dance Theatre (NCDT), 1976-1985
    - Contract, Work Plan, Questionnaire, Progress Report, Organizational Structure, 1976-1979 (Box 112)
    - Organizational Structure, 1976-1979, 2 folders (Box 112)
    - Organizational Development, 1976-1979, 2 folders (Box 112)
  - North Carolina Dance Theatre (NCDT), 1976-1985 (Box 113)
    - Organizational Development, 1976-1979 (Box 113)
    - Campaigns, 1976-1980, 3 folders (Box 113)
    - Marketing: Public Relations, 1976-1979 (Box 113)
    - Marketing: Printed Material, 1976-1979 (Box 113)
  - North Carolina Dance Theatre (NCDT), 1976-1985 (Box 114)
    - Marketing (con't): Special Events, Direct Mail 1976-1979 (Box 114)
    - Other: Board Meetings, 1977-1979, 2 folders (Box 114)
    - Contract, Questionnaire, Research, 1983-1984 (Box 114)
    - Structure, Long-range Plan-fund, 1981-1984 (Box 114)
    - Financials, 1979-1984 (Box 114)
    - Grantsmanship 1979-1984 (Box 114)
  - North Carolina Dance Theatre (NCDT), 1976-1985 (Box 115)
    - Hickory, 2 folders (Box 115)
    - Articles, 1980-1984 (Box 115)
    - News Clippings, Correspondence, 1984 (Box 115)
    - General, 1983 (Box 115)
  - North Carolina Museum of Art (NCMA), 1977-1978
    - Priorities/Work Plan, Questionnaire (Box 115)
    - Questionnaire (con't), Survey (Box 115)
  - North Carolina Museum of Art (NCMA), 1977-1978 (Box 116)
    - Survey and Focusing Process, 2 folders (Box 116)
    - Programs/Funding Requests, Budgets, Resources/Funding (Box 116)
    - Resources Development Activities and Solicitation (Box 116)
    - Solicitation (con't) (Box 116)
  - North Carolina Museum of Art (NCMA), 1977-1978 (Box 117)
    - Solicitations, Public Relations, Printed Material, Direct Mail (Box 117)
  - North Carolina School of the Arts (NCSA), 1974-1985
    - Contracts, Work Plan, 1974-1980 (Box 117)
    - Work Plan (Con't), Questionnaire, 1980-1981 (Box 117)
  - North Carolina School of the Arts (NCSA), 1974-1985 (Box 118)
    - Progress Reports, 1975-1982, 3 folders (Box 118)
  - North Carolina School of the Arts (NCSA), 1974-1985 (Box 119)
    - Progress Report (con't), 1979 (Box 119)
    - Organizational Structure, 1974-1980, 5 folders (Box 119)
  - North Carolina School of the Arts (NCSA), 1974-1985 (Box 120)
    - Organizational Structure, 1975-1980, 7 folders (Box 120)
  - North Carolina School of the Arts (NCSA), 1974-1985 (Box 121)
    - Organizational Structure, 1971-1982, 6 folders (Box 121)
    - Organizational Development, 1976-1981 (Box 121)
  - North Carolina School of the Arts (NCSA), 1974-1985 (Box 122)
    - Organizational Development, 1976-1984, 5 folders (Box 122)
    - Marketing:Public Relations, 1973-1979 (Box 122)
  - North Carolina School of the Arts (NCSA), 1974-1985 (Box 123)
    - Marketing, 1968-1982, 5 folders (Box 123)
    - General Correspondence, 1975-1978, 3 folders (Box 123)
  - North Carolina School of the Arts (NCSA), 1974-1985 (Box 124)
    - General Correspondence, 1979-1982, 4 folders (Box 124)
    - Other, 1977-1978 (Box 124)
    - NCSA/State: Ampersand Relationship and Campaign Progress, 1979-1982 (Box 124)
  - North Carolina School of the Arts (NCSA), 1974-1985 (Box 125)
    - NCSA/State and Ampersand Relationship and Campaign Progress (con't), 1979-1982 (Box 125)
    - Support Materials, 1975-1982 (Box 125)
    - Printed Materials, 1979-1980, 2 folders (Box 125)
    - State Committee Meetings, 1980 (Box 125)
    - Events, 1980-1981 (Box 125)
    - Governor's Dinner, 1981-1982 (Box 125)
  - North Carolina School of the Arts (NCSA), 1974-1985 (Box 126)
    - Statewide Resources, 1978-1982 (Box 126)
    - Major Proposals, Correspondence, 1979-1982 (Box 126)
    - Hickory Campaign, 1979-1981, 4 folders (Box 126)
    - Charlotte Campaign, 1980-1981 (Box 126)
  - North Carolina School of the Arts (NCSA), 1974-1985 (Box 127)
    - Charlotte Campaign, 1980-1982, 6 folders (Box 127)
    - Greensboro, Asheville, Shelby, High Point, 1980-81 (Box 127)
  - North Carolina School of the Arts (NCSA), 1974-1985 (Box 128)
    - High Point (con't), 1980-1981 (Box 128)
    - Raleigh-Durham-Chapel Hill, 1977-1982 (Box 128)
    - Gastonia, 1980-1981 (Box 128)
  - North Carolina School of the Arts (NCSA), 1974-1985 (Box 129)
    - Board of Visitors 1984 (Box 129)
    - Contract, Work Plan, Personnel Goals/Purpose, Financials, 1983-1984 (Box 129)
    - Research, 1983-1984, 2 folders (Box 129)
    - Fund Raising 1983-1984, 2 folders (Box 129)
    - Correspondence, 1983-1984 (Box 129)
  - North Carolina School of the Arts (NCSA), 1974-1985 (Box 130)
    - Correspondence, 1984, 2 folders (Box 130)
    - Potential Donors: A-Z, 1983-1984, 4 folders (Box 130)
    - Potential Donors: National, 1984 (Box 130)
  - North Carolina School of the Arts (NCSA), 1974-1985 (Box 131)
    - Potential Donors: National, 1984 (con't) (Box 131)
    - Potential Donors: State, 1984 (Box 131)
    - National Prospects, 1983-1984 (Box 131)
    - Long-range Plan, Budgets, Reports and Memoranda, National Donors, 1984-1985 (Box 131)
  - North Carolina School of the Arts (NCSA), 1974-1985 (Box 132)
    - Potential Donors, 1984-1985, 3 folders (Box 132)
  - North Carolina School of the Arts (NCSA), 1974-1985 (Box 133)
    - Report, 1983-84 and Proposal, 1984-1985 (Box 133)
    - Market Book, NCSA-State, 2 folders (Box 133)
  - North Carolina School of the Arts (NCSA), 1974-1985 (Box 134)
    - National Research, 3 folders (Box 134)
    - National-Low Priority, 3 folders (Box 134)
    - National-Pending (Box 134)
    - National-Approached (Box 134)
  - North Carolina School of the Arts (NCSA), 1974-1985 (Box 135)
    - Board of Visitors, 1983-1984, 2 folders (Box 135)
    - Stevens Center, 1982-1983 (Box 135)
  - North Carolina School of the Arts (NCSA), 1974-1985
    - Stevens Center, 1983 (con't), 3 folders (Box 136)
  - North Carolina School of the Arts (NCSA), 1974-1985 (Box 137)
    - Campaign Coordinating Book, 1979-1981, 2 folders (Box 137)
    - Correspondence, 1982-1985 (Box 137)
  - North Carolina School of the Arts (NCSA), 1974-1985 (Box 138)
    - Correspondence, 1985, 2 folders (Box 138)
  - North Carolina School of the Arts (NCSA), 1974-1985 (Box 139)
    - Campaigning Coordinating Book, 1979-1981 (Box 139)
    - Report and Proposal, 1983 (Box 139)
    - Reports to NCSA, 1965 (Box 139)
    - Progress Report, 1982 and Space Study, 1980 (Box 139)
    - Economic Impact Study, 1978 and Stevens Center (Box 139)
    - Development Records (Box 139)
    - In Partnership and Alumni Survey, 1978 (Box 139)
    - Workplace Dedication (Box 139)
  - North Carolina School of the Arts (NCSA), 1974-1985 (Box 140)
    - Donors-Unrestricted, 1984 (Box 140)
    - Donors-Scholarships, 2 folders (Box 140)
    - Chancellor Search, 1984, 2 folders (Box 140)
    - Charlotte, 1983-1984 (Box 140)
    - State, 1982-1984 (Box 140)
    - Stevens Center Articles, 1983 (Box 140)
    - Articles and Press Releases, 1978-1984 (Box 140)
    - Reports, 1985 (Box 140)
    - Stevens Center (Box 140)
    - Stevens Center: Articles, 1983 (Box 140)
  - North Carolina School of the Arts (NCSA), 1974-1985 (Box 141)
    - Graduates, Publicity (Box 141)
    - NCSA Workplace Dedication, April 1978 (Box 141)
    - Information Booklet (Box 141)
    - Meetings and Correspondence, 1984-1986 (Box 141)
    - Jazz Is, 1982 (Box 141)
    - Board of Visitors, 1983-1984 (Box 141)
    - Stevens Center (Bill in Congress), 1979 (Box 141)
    - Stevens Center: Brochures (Box 141)
    - Stevens Center: Clippings (Box 141)
    - Challenge Grant Follow-up, 1978-1981 (Box 141)
    - Five-year Plan, Contracts, Financial Statements (Box 141)
  - North Carolina School of the Arts (NCSA), 1974-1985 (Box 142)
    - Five-year Plan, Contracts. Financial Statements (con't) (Box 142)
  - North Carolina Symphony (NCS), 1978
    - The Case for Support (Box 142)
    - Contract, Work Plan, Questionnaire, Organizational Structure (Box 142)
    - Organizational Development (Box 142)
    - Marketing, 2 folders (Box 142)
    - Chicago Debut Planning, 1978 (Box 142)
  - North Carolina Symphony (NCS), 1978 (Box 143)
    - Chicago Debut Planning, 1978 (con't), 2 folders (Box 143)
    - Correspondence, 1978 (Box 143)
  - Old Salem, 1977-1981
    - Contract, Work Plan, Questionnaire (Box 143)
    - Marketing: Public Relations, Special Events (Box 143)
    - Old Salem, 1976-1978 (Box 143)
    - Progress Report, Organizational Structure (Box 143)
  - Old Salem, 1977-1981 (Box 144)
    - Contract, Organizational Structure, Organizational Development, 1981 (Box 144)
    - Organizational Development, 1975-1978 (con't), 2 folders (Box 144)
  - Old Salem, 1977-1981 (Box 145)
    - Organizational Development, 1975-1978 (con't) (5 folders), and General Correspondence, 1975-1979 (Box 145)
    - Other, 1976-1978 (Box 145)
  - Phoenix Organization, 1978
    - Contract, Workplan, Progress Report, Organizational Structure (Box 145)
  - Phoenix Organization, 1978 (Box 146)
    - Organizational Development, 2 folders (Box 146)
  - Piedmont Chamber Orchestra, 1978
    - Work Plan, Questionnaire, Structure (Box 146)
  - Piedmont Chamber Orchestra, 1978 (Box 147)
    - Research/Funding (Box 147)
  - Raleigh Cultural Arts Action Plan, 1984
    - Request for Proposal, Background, Long-Range Planning, 1984 (Box 147)
    - Facilities, 1979-1984 (Box 147)
    - Arts Foundation, City Gallery, Special Populations, 1981-1982 (Box 147)
  - Roanoak Project, 1982-1986 (Box 148)
    - Correspondence, 1982-1986, 3 folders (Box 148)
    - Proposal (Box 148)
  - Rockingham County Arts Council, 1983 (Box 148)
  - St. Johns Art Gallery, 1979-1980
    - Contract, Work Plan, Questionnaire, Organizational Structure, Organizational Development (Box 148)
    - Organizational Development (con't), Marketing, General Correspondence, Other (Box 148)
    - Blueprints (Box 148)
  - Salem College and Academy, 1981
    - Organizational Development (Box 148)
  - Salem College and Academy, 1981 (Box 149)
    - Organizational Development, 3 folders (Box 149)
    - Contract, Questionnaire, Organizational Structure (Box 149)
  - Sawtooth Center for Visual Design, 1984, 2 folders (Box 150)